BREAKING:
Ravens in a Real Mess, Folks!
Lamar Jackson's out with a hamstring
injury, and it's like the whole
team is saying, 'Sky is falling,
sky is falling!
' (chuckles) Cooper Rush, the new
starter, is like the calm in
the storm, saying, 'Hey, I've been
here before, it's all good!
' (sarcastically) Yeah, sure, buddy, you've
been here before.
in a different team, with a
different playbook, and with a better
haircut!
(laughs) Anyway, the Ravens are 1-3,
and it's getting ugly.
They've got nine players on the
injury list, including three Pro Bowlers.
The Texans are looking to beat
them for the first time since
2014.
Can the Ravens turn it around?
(shrugs) I'm not holding my breath.
Stay tuned, folks!